Guide to the Time Inc. records Bio files 3009.RG2
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Davidson, Spencer
- Davies, John Patton: [H.R. Luce]
- Davis, Anne
- Davis, Evelyn
- Davis, Floyd & Gladys
- Davis, Johanna
- Davis, Mary
- Davis, Myron H.: Pix & bio; Reminiscences: Loengard Interview 10/28/93; Misc
- Davis, Myron
- Davis, Noel
- Davis, Richard
- Davis, Richard D.
- Davis, Robert H (Bob)
- Davis, William G. Jr.: [H.R. Luce]
- Dawson, Robert J.
- Day, John F.: Pix & Bio
- DE
- Dealy, Francis X. (Bud)
- Dean, Loomis: Reminiscences [Life Anniv. 1986]; Reminiscences [Loengard Interview 11/4/93]
- Dean, Nicholas
- Deakins, Roger
- De Beausacq, Ingeborg
- Dawson, Charles J
- De Carava, Roy
- De Carvalho, George: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- De Clerque, E. Stevens: Pix & bio
- De Clerque, Steve(ns)
- De Gallo, Ursula Nadasdy
- Deford, Alexandra Miller (Alex)
- Degener, Jo(sephine) Marie-Christine
- Dehn, Monica: Pix & bio
- De La Cal, Martha
- Delaney, Patricia: Bio & pix [Empty]
- Delehanty, Hugh
- Delgado (Lozano), Rafael
- Del Solar, Daniel: Writings; Misc
- De Madariaga, Salvador: Sketches
- Demark, Richard
- DeMarchel, Patrick
- Demaree, Allan
- Demaree, Allan Thomas
- Demarest, Mike: [H.R. Luce]
- Demarest, Michael
- De Margitay, Gedeon
- De Meyer, Baron Adolf
- De Mott, John S.
- De Mott, John
- Denman, Joe C.
- Denman, Joe C Jr.
- De Patie, Edmond L
- Depinet, Ned E.: Pix & bio
- Desmond, Edward W.: Pix & bio
- Deutschman, Alan: Pix & bio
- De Rochemont, Louis: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio; Speeches; Reminiscences
- De Rochemont, Richard: Reminiscences; Pix & bio; Speeches; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- De Santis, Pasqualine
- Desmond, Edward W (Ned)
- Deutschman, Alan
- De Visser, John
- De Vosjoli, Phillippe
- De Voss, David
- De Voto, Bernard
- D'Honau, Charles
- D'Honau, Charles E
- Dibble, Allen Caneton: Reminiscences; Pix & bio
- Dick, Sheldon
- Dickerson, Ernest
- Diederich, Bernard
- Didion, Joan
- Diliberto, Gioia
- Dille, John M.: Pix & bio
- Dingman, Michael D.
- Di Sapio, Rosemarie
- Distler, Monya: Reminiscences
- Divver, Patricia: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio; Reminiscences
- Dix, Seldon: Bio & pix
- Djilas, Milovan
- DO - DY
- Dobell, Byron
- Dodge, Geoffrey A
- Dodge, Washington: Reminiscences
- Doerner, Bill
- Dohrn, Klaus: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Doisneau, Robert
- Dolan, Charles
- Dolan, Kevin L.
- Dolbern, David
- Dole, Henry: Pix & bio; Reminiscences; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Dolan, Barbara B.
- Dolan, Kevin L
- Dolben, David H.
- Dominis, John: Reminiscences [Loengard Interview 10/27/93]; Reminiscences [Life Anniv. 1986]; [H.R. Luce]
- Donald, Roger
- Donley, James W(alton)
- Donnelly, Caroline: Pix & bio
- Donnelly, Sally B
- Donoghue, James J.
- Donovan, Hedley: Bio; Pix; Meyer-Book on Culture in U.S. [Interview with H.D. 1967-72]; Files & Archives; Reminiscences [Video Tape][Oral History]; Reminiscences; Scholarship; Speeches [1965 & before]; Speeches [1966-1969]; Speeches [1970-1975]; Speeches [1976 & later]; Trips; [Donovan, Grunwald, Graves Dinner]; Writings; Misc
- Donovan, Hedley W: Sketches; Speeches [1968-]; Speeches [1962-1967]
- Donovan, Jere
- Doolittle, James H.
- D'Orazio, Sante
- Dorfman, Dan
- Dorion, Marta
- Dorion, Marta Fitzgerald
- Dorsey, Paul
- Dos Passos, John: (Including corres. with HRL) [H.R. Luce]
- Doscher, John
- Doubilet, David
- Douglas, John
- Dougherty, Margot: Pix & bio
- Dowd, Ann Reilly: Pix & bio
- Dowd, Jack
- Dowd, John F.: [H.R. Luce]
- Dowd, Maureen
- Dowling, George J.
- Dowling, John Graham: Pix & bio; Writings; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Downing, Donn
- Downs, Joan
- Downward, James G.
- Doyle, Robert J.: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio
- Dozier, Thomas A.: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Dragadzei, Peter
- Drake, Kathy
- Draper, Ernest M.
- Drapkin, Arnold
- Draz, Peter: Pix & bio
- Dreiman, David
- Dressler, Fred
- Drew, Robert: Pix & Bio; Misc
- Drew, Robert L.
- Dreyfuss, Henry
- Dreyfuss, Joel
- Dreyfus, Patricia
- Drooz, Daniel D.
- Drozdiak, William
- Drucker, Peter
- Du Bois, Cornelius: Pix & bio; Reminiscences; Speeches; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Dubois, L(arry) Clayton
- Duby, Gertrude
- Duffy, Martha M.
- Duffy, Martha
- Duffy, Michael: Pix & bio
- Duke, F. Du Sossoit: Misc [H.R. Luce]; Pix & bio; Reminiscences
- Dukmejian, Michael V.
- Dullagham, John: Reminiscences
- Dulles, Allen
- Dumaine, Brian
- Duffy, Michael
- Dumper, Robert S.
- Duncan, David Douglas: Pix & bio; Misc [1953 & before] [H.R. Luce]; Misc [1954 & later][H.R. Luce]
- Duncan, Kenn
- Duncan, Richard L.
- Duncan, Richard L (Dick)
- Dunn, Betty
- Dunn, James J.: Pix & bio
- Dunn, Jeffrey D.
- Dunn, John
- Dunn, Mary
- Dunne, John Gregory: Pix & bio
- Durdin, Peggy (Mrs Tillman)
- Durniak, John
- Durham, Michael
- Durniak, John
- Durrell, Richard: Speeches
- Durrell, Richard J
- Durrell, Lawrence
- Dutka, Elaine
- Dworkin, Peter
- E
- Eames, Charles: Sketches
- Earnshaw, Spencer W.
- Eaton, William H. (Doc): Reminiscences
- Ecker, Allan B.
- Edelman, Marion Wright
- Edelmann, Heinz
- Edey, Maitland A.: Pix & bio
- Edey, Maitland: Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Edgerton, Harold Eugene
- Edgerton, Harold
- Edgerton, Jerry
- Edmondson, Robert J.
- Edwards, Ken
- Eftimiades, Maria
- Eggleston, Charles Richard
- Ehrbar, A F
- Eichler, Joseph L: Sketches; Eichelberger, Gen. R.L.
- Eichmann, Adolph
- Eiselle, Paul
- Eisen, Gail
- Eisenberg, Richard
- Eisendrath, Charles
- Eisendrath, David B. Jr.
- Eisenhower, Milton
- Eisenstaedt: Awards and Honors [Misc]
- Eisenstaedt, Alfred: Sketches; Bio [1945-1989]; Bio [1990-]; Pix
- Eisenstaedt Time Inc Memorial
- Eisenstaedt, Alfred: Obituaries; Reminiscences; Reminiscences [Loengard Interview 1/18/92]; Reminiscences [Life Anniv. 1986]; Misc [H.R. Luce]
- Eitingon, Lee
- Elgort, Arthur
- Eliot, Alexander: Pix & bio; Speeches; Misc
- Elisofon, Eliot: Pix & bio; Speeches; Misc [H.R. Luce]; Sketches
- Elliman, Don
- Elliman, Donald M Jr.
- Elliot, Charles
- Elliot, Osborn
- Ellison, Robert J
- Elmer-Dewitt, Philip: Pix & bio
- Elson, John
- Elson, John T.
- Elson, Robert: Pix & bio; Misc [H.R. Luce]; Speeches
- Elson, Robert T.
- Ely, Vincent: Pix & bio; Reminiscences
- Emmett, Jay
- Engle, Paul
- English, Chris
- Englund, Steven
- *****New Naming Method Below*****
- Eppridge, William E.
- Eppridge, Bill
- Epstein, Rose Lansman
- Ermansons, Taiga
- Eskelund, Karl J.
- Ernst, Morris
- Evans, Nancy
- Evans, Walker
  Six folders, one folder includes "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Ewald, William F.
- Ewing, William A.
- Everly, William A.
- Eyerman, J.R.
- Eyerman, Jay R.
- FA
- Faas, Horst
- Faber, Nancy Gay
- Fadiman, Anne
- Fadiman, Clifton
- Fadiman, Clifton (Kip)
- Fahey, John M.
- Falk, Samuel
- Farb, Nathan
- Farbman, Harry
- Farber, Manny
- Farbman, Nat
- Farbman, Nat R.
- Farmer, Gene
- Farbar, John C.
- Farrell, Barry
- Farrell, Dan(iel)
- Farrell, Edgar H. (Ted)
- Faulkner, Douglas (Doug)
- Farro, Eugene F.
- Faurer, Louis
- Fay, Martha
- Fay, Toni G.
- Fayard, Judy
- Fein, Nat
- Feininger, Andreas B.L.
- Feininger, Andreas
- Feinstein, Harold
- Feldstein, Mark
- Fellig, Arthur H.
- Felker, Clay
- Fenn, Albert
- Fenn Family
- Fenner, Elizabeth
- Fenton, Roger
- Fentress, Simmons
- Fernandez, Mary
- Fernandez, Benedict J(ose)
- Ferrari, Christina
- Ferrato, Donna
- Ferrer, Jose M., III
- Ferrer, Jose M. III (Joe)
- Ferorelli, Enrico
- Fessler, Loren
- FI
- Fickett, Homer
- Field, Harold
- Field, Harold C.
- Field, Michael
- Fielder, Wilson
- Fields, Kathy
- Fierman, Jaclyn
- Finch, Edward C.K.
  One folder with "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Fink, Conrad
- Fink, Laurence B.
- Fink, Peter
- Finkelstein, Edward S.
- Finkelstein, Melvin
- Finney, Paul
- Firestone, Russell A(llen) Jr.
- Fischbeck, Frank
- Fisher, Anne B.
- Fischer, Carl
- Fischer, David E. (Dave)
- Fischer, Dean
- Fisher, Lucy
- Fischer, Peggy
- Fischer, Pete
- Fisher, Regina
- Fisher, Roswell E.
- Fisher, William E.
- Fisler, Robert
- Fistere, John
  Three folders, one folder includes "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Fitzgerald, Edward
- Fitzgerald, Robert Stuart
- Fitzgerald, Robert
- Fixx, Calvin
- Flaherty, Thomas H. Jr.
- Flaherty, Tom
- Flamini, Roland
- Flanagan, Dennis
- Flanner, Janet
- Fleischer, Jack
- Flink, Stanley
- Flint, Ruth
- Flippo, Chet
- Flora, H.B. (Bud)
- Florcruz, Jaime
- Florea, Johnny
- Flynn, John
- FO
- Fodor, Denis J.A.
- Foley, Bill
- Fondren, Lee
- Foote, Timothy
- Forbath, Peter
- Forbes, J. Wendell
  Two folders, one folder includes "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Forbes, Robert L(aidlaw) (Bob)
- Forbis, William
- Forbis, Bill (William H)
- Force, Henrietta
- Ford, Charles Henri
- Ford, Enfield (Flicky)
- Ford, Mark
- Ford, Nancy & Ogg, Ruth
- Forester, Max
- Forma, Warren
- Ford, Enfield (Flicky)
- Forman, Harrison
- Forman, Stanley J.
- Forss, George
- Fortinberry, C. Lane
- Fortinberry, Lane
  Two folders, one folder has "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Fowler, Henry H.
- Fowles, John Winston III
- Fowles, Winston
- Fox, Thomas C. (Tom)
- Fox, Francis S. (Frank)
- FR
- Frady, Marshall
- Frame, Peter W.
- Frank, Amanda
- Frank, Robert
- Frank, Rosemary
- Fraser, Mary
  Four folders, one folder has "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Franklin, Benjamin
- Franklin, Ben A.
- Frausto, Ramon
- Franklin, Jean
- Frazier, George
- Frazier, George F.
- Fredenthal, David
- Freed, Albert
  One folder
- Freed, Leonard
- Freedgood, Seymour
- Freeman, Gaylord
- Freeman, Gaylord A. Jr.
- Frehm, Ron(ald)
- Freidrich, Otto
- Fremd, Mary Elizabeth
- French, Art
- French, Winsor
- Freni, Al
- Frey, John
- Frey, John J. (Jack)
- Frey, Rudi
- Friedland, Seymour
- Friedlander, Lee
- Friedman, Frederica S.
- Friedman, William
- Friedrich, Emily
- Friedrich, Otto
- Friend, David
- Frings, Klaus
- Frissell, Toni
- Frizell, Bernard
- Frith, Francis
- Frodin, Reuben
- Fromson, Brett Duval
- Froslid, Kenneth
- Frook, John
- Fuchs, Michael
- Fuerbringer, Otto
  Nine folders, one folder has "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Fuller, (Richard) Buckminster
  Nine folders, two folders with "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Fulton, Hamish
- Furla, Spero
- Furlong, William
- Furst, Austin O. Jr.
- Furth, Albert L.
- Furth, Albert
- Furth, Albert L.
  Three folders, one folder has "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Fusco, Paul
- GA
- Gaetano, Nicholas
- Gaines, James R.
- Gaines, James R (Jim)
- Gaines, Jim
- Gahr, David
- Galbraith, John Kenneth
  Eight folders, one folder with "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Gallagher, John
- Galbraith, John Kenneth
- Gallagher, William J.
- Gallagher, Bernard
- Gallagher, Carole
- Gallagher, William M
- Gallo, Frank
- Galvin, Ruth (Mehrtens)
- Gangel, Richard
- Ganis, Sydney M
- Gannes, Stuart
- Garcia, Cristina
- Garcia, Moises
- Garcia Rodero, Christina
- Gardephe, Paul
- Gardiner, Peter M.
- Gardner, Alexander
- Gardner, John W.
  Nine folders, one folder has "H.R. Luce" Stamp
- Gardner, Mart
- Garey, Robert
- Garfield, Harry & Helen
- Garin, Michael
- Garnett, William
- Garretto, Paolo
- Garin, Michael
- Garrison, Lloyd M.
- Gart, Murray J.
- Gary, Romain
- Gates, Artemus L.
- Gates, Mrs. Artemus L.
- Gaudio, Gaetano (Tony)
- Gauger, Marcia
- Gault, John F.
- Gawenda, Michael
- GE
- Geer, William D.
- Geeslin, Campbell
- Gehr, Herbert
- Geisenheimer, Susan
- Geline, Robert (Bob)
- Gellhorn, Martha
- Gelman, Steve
- George, Philip Basil Jr.
- Gerbrandt, Larry
- Gerry, Valerie
- Gescheidt, Alfred
- Gettell, Richard Glenn
- Gibbs, Eric Leon
  Two folder, one folder has "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Gibbs, Eric
- Gibbs, Nancy
- Giblin, Austin
- Gibney, Frank Bray
- Gibney, Frank
- Gibson, Ralph
- Gigli, Ormand
- Gilbert, Frederick S.
- Gilbert, Frederick S. (Fritz)
- Gilbert, Ronald
- Gilchrist, Jane
- Gill, Allan
- Gill, Jill
- Gilman, Lois
- Girard, Alexander H.
- Gissen, Max
- Githens, William
- Gleason, Charles L. (Jr.)
- GL
- Glanzman, Louis
- Glasgow, Robert W.
- Gleason, Charles
- Gleaves, Suzanne
- Glenn, Jack
- Glessman, Louis
- Glessmann, Louis R.
- Glinn, Burt
- Glinn, Burton S.
- Glusker, Irwin
- Godfrey, Mark
- Godfrey, Raymond
- Gold, Stuart W.
- Gold, William J.
- Gold, William Jay
- Goldberg, Danny
- Goldblatt, Burt
- Golden, Frederic
- Golden, Frederic (Fred)
- Goldman, Arthur
- Goldman, Eric F.
- Goldman, Marvin
- Goldsborough, Anna G.
- Goldsborough, Laird S.
  Three folders, two folders with "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Goldsborough, James O(liver)
- Goldsmith, Arthur
- Goldsmith, Lynn
- Goldstein, Robert
- Golestan, Kaveh
- Gomel, Bob
- Goodgame, Dan
- Goodhue, Ruth (Chasteney)
- Gooding, Judson
- Goodman, Ezra
- Goodman, Mark S.
- Goodman, Jordan E.
- Goodrich, Henry C.
- Goodnow, David
- Goolrick, Bill
- Gorbaty, Norman
- Gordon, Leah
- Gordon, Pat(ricia)
- Gordon, Robert C.
- Gossage, John
- Gorey, Hays
- Gouldthorpe, Kenneth A.
- Goro, Fritz W.
- Goro, Herb
- Gottfried, C. Manfred
  Eight folders, two folder have "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Gottscho, Samuel H.
- Goude, Jean-Paul
- Gouldthorpe, Kenneth
- Gouzenko, Igor
- Gown, Emmet
- GR
- Grace, Mary
- Grad, Peter
- Graebner, Walter
  Six folders, one folder has "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Grafton, William D.
- Graham, David
- Graham, James
- Graham, Tim
- Grant, Allan
- Grant, James G.
- Grant, Zalin
- Gratz, Louis P.
- Graves, Eleanor
- Graves, Ralph
- Graves, Robert
- Gray, Paul
- Gray, Tam
- Gray, William P.
- Gray, William P. Jr.
- Greenblatt, Matt
- Grehan, Farrell
- Greene, Matthew
- Green, Timothy
- Greene, Milton H.
- Greenfeld, Karl Taro
- Greenleaf, Kenneth T.
- Greenfield, James L.
- Greenfield, Lois
- Greenfield-Sanders, Timothy
- Greenwald, John
- Greenwalt, Crawford H.
- Greenway, David
- Greer, Gayle
- Greer, Guy E.
- Grehan, Farrell
- Griffin, Jack
- Griffin, Michael
- Griffin, William Vincent
  Four folders, two folders have "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Griffin, William
- Griffith, Thomas
  Eight folders, two folders have "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Griffiths, Eldon
- Griffith, Thomas (Tom)
- Griffiths, Philip Jones
- Griggs, Lee
- Griggs, Northam Lee
- Griswold, Whitney
- Groden, Robert J.
- Groner, Alex
- Groover, Jan
- Groskinsky, Henry
- Gross, Ken
- Gross, Peter
- Grossman, Alan
- Grossman, Henry
- Groth, John
- Grotz, Paul
- Grover, James Allen
  Eleven folders, eight folders with "H.R. Luce" stamp and one folder with A/V materials
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. Labeled "MAG's Speech at staff meeting - year ? early 70's"
- Grover Family
- Gruin, Frederick
- Grum, Clifford
- Grum, Clifford Julian
- Grundberg, Andy
- Grunwald, Henry Anatole
  Fifteen folders, two folders with "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Grunwald Family
- Grunwald, Henry Anatole
- Grunwald, Henry
- Grunwald's Files
- Grunwald Papers Request
- Grunwald, Henry Anatole
- Grunwald, Lisa
  One folder, marked empty
- Grunwald, Louise
- Gruson, Kerry L
- Gschwind, Max
- Gundy, Bradley B.
- Gunn, William
- Gup, Ted
- Gussenhoven, Jean C. (Nini)
- Guttman, William M.
- Guzzardi, Walter
  Ten folders, eight folders with "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Guzzardi, Walter Jr.
- Gwynne, S.C. ("Sam")
- HA
- Haas, David R.
- Haas, Ernest
- Hadden, Family
- Haber, Joyce
- Hadden, Briton
- Haeberle, Ronald L.
- Hagel, Otto & Johanna
- Hagel, Otto
- Hagel, Mrs. Otto
- Haggerty, Gerald G.
- Haight, Catherine
- Haire, John E.
- Haje, Peter R.
- Halasz, Piri
- Haldeman, H.R.
- Hale, E.V.
- Hale, Paul E.
- Hale, William Harlan
- Halevy, David
- Hall, E.S.
- Hall, Lee
- Hall, Ted
- Halle, Katherine
- Hallenbeck, John
- Haller, Scot
- Hallett, Bruce
- Hallett Family
- Halami, Robert (Bob)
- Halper, Sam
- Halperin, Mark
- Halsman, Philippe
- Halstead, Dirck
- Halvorsen, Rosalind
- Hamblin, Cora
- Hamblin, Dora Jane
- Hamblin, Dora Jane (Dodie)
- Hamilton, Alexander (Papers)
- Hammack, Felix M.
- Hamilton, Edward A.
- Hamman, Mary
- Hamil, Katherine
- Hammill, Katherine
- Hamman, Mary
- Hanes, John W.
  Two folders, one folder marked empty
- Hannifin, Jerry
- Hansen, Marie
- Hansen, Peter
- Hanson, Chuck
- Hanson, Peter
- Han Suylin (Dr. Elizabeth Comber)
- Harbison, Georgia
- Harbutt, Charles
- Hard, Eleanor (Lake)
- Harding, Harry
- Hardin, Louis (Moondog)
- Hardy, David
- Hardy, Hugh
- Hardy, Jerome S.
- Hardy, Rex
- Hardy, Rex Jr.
- Hare, David Meredith
- Harkness, E.S.
- Harkness, William Hale
- Harman, Carter
- Harrer, Heinrich
- Harriman, Averell
- Harrington, Angela Janklow
- Harrington, Phillip
- Harris, Bill
- Harris, George T.
- Harris, Louis (& associates)
- Harris, Marlys J.
- Harris, Tommy J.
- Harris, William B.
  Two Folders, one folder has "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Harrison, Richard Edes
- Harrison, Wallace K(irkman)
- Hartig, John J.
- Hart, Lianne
- Hart, Moss
- Hartman, Erich
- Harvey, John F.
- Haskell, Douglas
- Hatch, Henry
- Hattersley, Ralph
- Hattersley, Robert C.
- Haugh, Brendan
- Hauser, Gustave
- Havemann, Ernest C.
- Hawthorne, Peter
- Hayes, James B.
- Hayes, James B(endedict) (Jim)
- Hayward, Charles
- Hayworth, James O.
- Hazen, Joseph
- Hazen, Joseph H(arrington)
- Hazen, Joseph C. Jr.
- HE
- Heard, Alexander
- Heard Family
- Hearst, William Randolph
- Heck, Harriet
- Hecker, Arthur
- Heffner, Lee
- Heilbroner, Robert
- Heilperin, Michael A.
- Heinemann, Richard
- Heinecken, Robert
- Heinke, Edwin Charles
- Heiskell, Andrew
  Fifty seven folders, two folders have "H.R. Luce" stamp and two folders include A/V material
  1 audiocassette: analog. Case is labeled "Heiskell at Fortune Sales Meeting, 1976" and cassette is labeled "The Great Company Today and Tomorrow, Andrew Heiskell"
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. Case marked "Speech by Andrew Heiskell, after staff presentation, March 28, 1968, a.m" "Speech is preceded by: 1) 4 sec. of applaus 2)5 sec. silence, then speech"
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 5 in. In a manilla envelope, marked "Vivistiles A Heiskell 34," with a note attached. The note indicates the contents of the tape, the running time, the speed to play reel, and a summary.
- Heiskell Family
- Heiskell, Marian
- Heisler, Gregory
- Held, Jean
- Hellebrand, Nancy
- Heller, Joseph
- Hellman, Geoffrey
- Heminway, Stuart
- Henderson, Bruce
- Henderson, Lady Mary
- Henle, Fritz
- Hengstenberg, Ann
- Henricks, Jay
- Henry, Ed (Edgar)
- Henry, William A. III
- Henry, William J.
- Herbert, Charles
- Hering, H. Brooks
  Two folders, one folder with "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Herrera, Philip
- Herrmanns, Ralph
- Hersey, John Richard
- Hess, Mark
- Hess, Richard
- Hewlett, Roger S.
- Heyman, Ken
- Heyworth, James O.
- Hickey, Jr., Thomas J.
- Hicks, Jim
- Hicks, Wilson
  Six folders, one folder with "H.R. Luce" stamp and one folder with A/V material. 1/4 in. tape. Includes a note:
  "Bob: This tape contains mainly our 'preface'. It contains matter not in the nature of editing and perhaps enlarging on the original but matter which we could not resist articulating. We taped only one ride or we were not too familiar with the wollen-rak. Now we're going to use a Noreleo which is simpler. We want to get this tape off to you to let you know we have our project under way. Will have more tape on the way shortly.
  Bill Wilson
  P.S.-You'll find the first few feet of this tape a litte indistinct, but it picks up agter a moment or two.
  Wtt 4-4-'70
  Bill Howland Willson Hicks"
- Higgins, Chester Jr.
- Higley, Karen
- Hiland, Bruce R.
- Hiland, R. Bruce
- Hildyard, Jack
- Hill, Allan
- Hill, Ernest R.
- Hill, Mrs.
- Hill, Stephanie D.
- Hillenbrand, Barry
- Hiller, Lejaren
- Hillman, Serrell
- Hiltbrand, David
- Himmelfarb, Harvey
- Hincks, John M.
- Hine, Lewis W(ickes)
- Hiro
- Hirsch, George A.
- Hiss, Alger
- Hiss, Alger (Priscilla Fansler Hopson)
- Hiss, Priscilla
- HO
- Hoagland, John
- Hobbs, Virginia
- Hobbing, Enno
- Hobson, Laura
- Hobson, Laura Z.
- Hobson, Wilder
- Hockaday, Newton
- Hodgins, Eric
  Eight folders, three folders have "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Hodgins, Eleanor Treacy
- Hodgson, James
- Hoefer, James B.
- Hoeft, William
- Hoffman, Bernard
- Hoffman, Paul Gray
- Hofer, Evelyn
- Hoffman, Ethan
- Hoffman, Paul
- Hoffman, Paul Gray
  Three folders with "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Hogan, Charles D.
- Hogarth, Paul
- Hoglund, Rudy (Rudolph)
- Holcomb, Richard
- Holland, Gerald
- Hollister, Paul
- Holman, William W.
  Four folders, one has "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Holmes, Geoffrey A.
- Holmes, Martha
- Holmes, Nigel
- Holmes, Steven
- Holt, Donald
- Holzman, Jac
- Honegger, Pierre
- Honneus, William Stone
- Honeyman, Robert B.
- Honneus, William S.
  Four folders, one folder with "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Hood, Alexander
- Hooper, Bayard
- Hooper, Bill
  One folder which includes A/V material.
  1 computer disc (CD-R): digital; 4 3/4 in. Cd jacket has a sticker which says: "Time-Life Alumni Society; October 19, 2010; Bill Hooper - Time Inc. Archives" and the cd is marked "Bill Hooper TLAA 10.19"
- Hoover, Dorothy
- Hoover, Eleanor
- Hoover, Lawrence
- Howard, Jane
- Hopkins, Anne
- Hopkins, Peter
- Hopkinson, Peter
- Hopkins, Peter S.
- Hopkins, William
- Hopper, Edward
- Hopper, Hedda
- Horan, Harold J.T.
- Horn, Florence Retzer
- Horne, Monica
- Horner, Matina S.
- Horner, Matina
- Hornik, Richard
- Horowitz, Edward
- Horst, Horst P (Paul)
- Hotchner, A.E.
- Howard, Jane
- Howard, Marjorie
- Howe, Elias
- Howard, Roy W.
- Howard, John
- Howe, Larry
- Howell, John
- Howell, John D.
- Howland, William S.
  Three folders, two folder have "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Howlett, Phillip G.
- Hoyt, George W.
- Hsieh, S.T.
- Hubbard, Fred
- Huet, Henri
- Huey, John
- Huey, John W. Jr.
- Huff, Kay L.
- HU
- Hughes, Edward
- Hughes, Emmet
- Hughes, Emmet John
- Hughes, Howard
- Hughrd, Robert
- Hujar, Peter
- Hulburd, David
  Three folders, two folders have "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Hulburd, David W. Jr.
- Hull, Jon
- Hummerstone, Robert G. (Bob)
- Humphrey, George M.
- Hunt, George P.
- Hunt, George
- Hunt, George Pinney
- Hunt, George P.
  Three folders, one folder with "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Hunt, Pat
- Hunt, Patricia
- Hurd, Peter
- Hurd, James Francis (Frank)
- Hurlimann, Martin
- Hurst, D'Orsey
- Hush, Paul W.
- Hutchins, Ross E.
- Huxley, Julian
- Huxtable, Ada Louise
- Hydorn, Bart
- Hyland, Thomas S. (Tom)
- Hyman, Eliot
- Hyman, Mervin
- I
- Iker, Sam R.
- Illson, Dorothy
- Ingalls, David
- Ingels, Evan
- Ingels, Evan
- Ingersoll, Ralph McAllister
- Ingersoll, Ralph II
- Ingersoll, Ralph McAllister
- Ingersoll, Ralph
- Ingersoll, Ralph McAllister
- Ingraham, Reg
- Iooss, Walter
- Irving, Clifford
- Irving, Wendell D.
- Irwin, Leigh
- Isaacson, Walter
- Isozaki, Arata
- Iyer, Pico
- Iwasaki, Carl
- Iwaski Family (Mitsubshi Family)
- Iyer, Pico
- JA
- Jack, Marjorie
- Jacker, Corinne
- Jackson, Alan R.
- Jackson, Ann
- Jackson, Anthony
- Jackson, C.D.
  Thirty one folders, sixteen folders have "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Jackson, C(harles) D(ouglas)
- Jackson, Charlie
- Jackson, Charles P.
- Jackson, David S.
- Jamieson, Ed(ward) L.
- Jackson, Donald
- Jackson, Edward
- Jackson, James
- Jackson, Jesse
- Jackson, Schuyler
- Jacobs, Fenno (Charles)
- Jacobs, Jane
- Jacobs, Gloria
- Jacoby, Annalee Whitmore
- Jacoby, Melville
- Jaeger, Carl
- Jaeger, Carl G.
- Jaeger, Hugo
- Jalet, Nancy
- James, Geoffrey
- James, Juanita
- James, P.D.
- James, Sidney L.
- James, Tim
- Jamieson, Edward L.
- Janeway, Eliot
  Eleven folders, three folders have "H.R. Luce" stamp
- Janos, Leo
  Two folders, one folder marked [empty]
- Janssen, Peter A.
- Jarche, James
- Jaroff, Leon
- Jarvis, Jeff
- Jaworski, Michele M.
- Jay, John
- Jeffreys, Willie
- Jenkisson, John
- Jensen, Oliver
- Jerome, Jim
- Jessup, John K.
- Jewett, Lynda
- Jessup, John K(nox)
- JO
- Joel, Yale
- Jones, Landon
- Johnson, Frank H.
- Johnson, John
- Johnson, Keith R.
- Johnson, Lynn
- Johnson, Malcom
- John, A.L.
- Johnson, Marguerite
- Johnson, Philip C.
- Johnson, Robert Livingston
- Johnson, Robin (Robert)
- Johnson, Roy S.
- Johnson, William W.
- Johnson, William A.
- Johnson, William W(eber)
- Johnston, Harry M.
- Johnston, Mary
- Johnston, Richard W.
- Johnston, Mary E.
- Johnston, Harry
- Johnstone, Roger A.
- Jones, Alfred Winslow
- Jones, Beverley
- Johnstone, Roger A.
- Jones, Charlotte Schiff
- Jones, Cranston
- Jones, Cranston (Cran)
- Jones, Cranston E.
- Jones, Edward F.
- Jones, George Edward
- Jones, Joseph Marion
- Jones, Joe
- Jones, Landon, Y.
- Jones, Robert
- Jones, Quincy